Want a drink?
Matière-san said you were up here.
It’s nice. Thanks.
You okay?
I’m okay...
Navi, what kind of Pokémon do you like?
Uh...
What do I do?! I can’t pick!
Gotcha...
Hey!
How did you two choose
your first Pokémon?
Um... This little one picked me
during my school interview!
School, huh...?
We’d been together for a long time,
but I just couldn’t choose on my own.
But then Wanival ended up being
the one who picked me.
That little guy picked you?!
Sure did.
That’s so nice...
Navi loves Pokémon so much
that she just can’t pick one...
I understand the feeling.
So Matière gave it to me,
for when it’s time to grab hold of my dream...
Your Dream Ball, you mean...?
Yeah.
That’s why it was important...
Ready, set, and... GO! READY! GO!
We’re in top-notch mode
You’re not alone, you know?
Put our palms together, raise them high, and let our lights unite
pOCket Monsters
Wonder Voyage
In rain, gales, or even blizzards
We can laugh together as friends
All of the gaps in the Index
let’s fill them in bit by bit
If you’re trying to be someone else
Don’t think like that
You’re fine just as you are
Don’t lose yourself
Recollect on what’s in your pocket
This is what makes us strong
A heartfelt bond that will never fade
Ready, set, and...
GO! READY! GO!
We’re in top-notch mode
You’re not alone, you know?
Let’s fly, higher and higher!
It’s fine to make mistakes
just rest your wings
When you’ve caught your breath
you can fly off once more!
Come along with us, oh-oh
Voltteccers
Pass the endlessly turning seasons,
and venture into brand-new skies
A Dream Ball For You!
It’s morning, Navi.
I’m heading out on morning patrol.
I’ll skip it today...
Everyone else said
they’re coming along.
Hmph...
Come retrace the route we searched
for Melecie yesterday. Maybe we could find it.
I’m coming!
First, I gotta get
the coffee ready, right?
That’s right!
Everyone, good morning!
Good morning, Navi!
Good morning!
Good morning.
Sleep well?
Everyone, get ready for a patrol!
Yeawww...
Ult... Don’t respond with a yawn.
You really are a little kid!
Wuzzat?!
This is the area where we
chased after Melecie yesterday, right?
Yeah.
Maybe this isn’t where I lost it...
Hey, you guys...
What’s the matter?
I see. Of course.
Dot, I have a request for Wanival.
What is it?
Could you wash away this sludge?
Got it.
Wanival! Aqua Cutter!
Wanival’s so cool!
They were having trouble
getting through...
How did you know that?
Fluff told her!
You two are always
on the same page, eh?
Yeah! Fluff’s always helping me out!
What’s wrong, Subomie?
A Shishiko!
The Subomie are in danger!
We’ve gotta save ‘em! Cap!
Let’s go, Yamirami!
Isn’t that great, Subomie?
Thank you,
Cap and Yamirami.
Bye-bye!
There really are wild Pokémon
in all sorts of places...
Yeah. I think Pokémon
must love this city, too.
What a mess...
It’s still not fixed?
Ms. Detective!
Do you have a moment?
Sure, what is it?
My apartment building
had a blackout...
Got it.
Denryu!
She says this apartment building
has had a blackout.
If you would, Denryu-chan.
Here we go, Denryu.
Shine down the light
of the great sun!
Mega Evolve!
Oh, thank goodness!
Thank you, Denryu!
Fixing a blackout with Mega Evolution...
There she goes again,
always wastin’ Mega Evolution...
It’s not a waste!
It’s to help people. Right, Denryu?
Thank you,
Ms. Detective and Denryu-chan!
You’re welcome.
It’s like Matière-san is
the city’s handywoman.
Yeah. Being a detective
seems like a wonderful job.
She spends every day just like this,
keeping the peace in Miare City.
So? Awesome, right?
And why are you bragging?
Smells great!
Navi’s hungry!
Think it’s time
we take a little break?
Mmm, mega-tasty!
Here you go!
Your special coffee milk, miss!
Thank you!
Ahh! It really is best fresh!
That’s the special coffee milk?
Yeah! Oh! Right, right!
This plaza’s where Matière
first told me about coffee milk!
You’re right.
Wasn’t this the place where we first met?
Matière and Fluff seemed like they were having
so much fun, so I decided to stay with them!
Is that right?
Yeah! Navi’s been playing with
the Pokémon in Miare City so long,
she doesn’t remember
what she did before that!
Which is why I asked Navi
to become my assistant.
And I was like, “Leave it to me!”
Aww...
Where could my Dream Ball
have gotten to...?
Look out, Navi!
Huh?
Navi, are you okay?!
Metamon?
Why is it here?!
I met you before! On the ship!
Huh?
This is...
Navi’s Dream Ball!
Thank you!
I mean it... Thank you...
Metamon had the Dream Ball?
Of course! So you dropped it
on the Brave Asagi yesterday!
Isn’t that great, Navi?
Yeah!
Metamon, you okay?!
It looks like it’s hungry!
Want a drink too?
You like it? Navi loves it, too!
They look like they’re having fun!
They’re good friends with Metamon!
It transformed into her tail!
That’s Metamon’s signature move.
I get it!
Turning into Trimmien’s hat, and Masquernya’s tail...
It plays by transforming into all sortsa stuff, huh?
That’s so nice...
Yay!
Now, back to patrolling!
Navi’ll give you the tour!
This place’s my home turf.
I know more than you ever could.
Right, Yamirami?
Navi’s not gonna be beat!
Let’s go, Metamon!
Navi! It’s about time we head back!
Okay!
You can turn into anything...
I’m so jealous.
Metamon, you go adventuring
with Cap and everyone, right?
That’s so nice...
Navi wants to go visit all sortsa places,
and see all sortsa Pokémon she’s never seen before, too!
Navi’d probably find it, then...
What Navi wants to do...
Navi’s dream... Yeah, for sure!
Ahh, I’m beat...
Thank you.
You really helped us out there.
Right, Fluff?
Thank you, too.
It was a lot of fun.
I learned a ton. About the wild Pokémon
living in the city, and other stuff too!
And we found the Dream Ball as well.
Thanks for looking for it with me!
Sorry for the wait!
The Brave Asagi’s finished resupplying!
Guess it’s about time you get going.
Yeah. See ya ‘round, Matière.
Thank you for all your help.
Matière-san,
your cooking was delicious.
Glad to hear it.
Feel free to visit again anytime.
Everyone, take care!
Metamon, thank you!
We’ll see you, then!
Goodbye!
See ya!
Bye-bye!
pOCket Monsters
Wonder Voyage
Welcome home!
We’re home!
Have fun in Miare?
Yeah, it was a lovely place!
There were loads of Pokémon, too!
How did it feel being back
in your hometown?
It was a’ight!
Same as it ever was, anyhow!
We’re all prepped
and ready to go, too!
Well then, let’s set off!
Yeah!
Let’s go, Cap!
Ah, so you were up here.
You’ve found it then, eh, Navi?
Huh?
What do you mean?
Your dream.
Navi’s... dream?
Yeah. Fluff let me know how you feel.
Fluff did...?
To tell the truth...
I realized that I’d been pampering you.
Matière?
When we’re together,
I end up babying you more than I do anyone else.
Why... are you saying that now?
Because now’s my only chance to.
Ever since you first spotted that airship up here,
you haven’t stopped shining.
Shining?
And... someone found it for you, right?
“When the time comes to grab hold of your dream...”
That time is now, wouldn’t you say?
I did feel it was a bit early for you,
but I want to put your feelings first.
What you want to see...
What you want to do...
The Pokémon you want to be with when you leave...
Because I knew you would leave someday.
That’s... now...
You’ve gotta grab hold of it
with your Dream Ball!
I’ll be right back!
Take care.
Wait up!
What a lovely city it was.
You know it!
Miare’s the strongest!
Wait up!
Kairyu?!
Metamon!
You came back for me... Metamon...
Navi wants to go with you!
With Metamon and everyone else!
Hey!
Navi.
Mm-hm.
We don’t always pick our Pokémon.
Pokémon can pick us, too.
I bet you’ll be just fine, Navi!
Navi thinks you’re amazing, Metamon!
You can be all sorts of things!
Navi wants to do
all sorts of things, too!
And with you,
Metamon, I think I can!
So...
So, will you...
...stay with me?
Metamon!
Thank you for finding me.
Let’s be friends, Metamon!
Congrats, Navi and Metamon!
Yeah!
I have a request for
all you Rising Voltteccers!
Navi wants to go on adventures
with Metamon on the Brave Asagi!
Good morning!
So cute!
It looks great on you,
and on Metamon!
Thank you, Matière!
And take this, too.
Navi’s own Smartphone Rotom!
Now, you’re all set for travel!
Yeah!
Good morning,
Navi and Matière-san!
Good morning!
Ooh, that’s a lovely outfit!
It looks great on you!
Yeah! Navi loves it, too!
Whoa! You were in there, Metamon?
Yup! It’s great, right?!
Well then, Navi...
Greet the Captain of the Brave Asagi!
Pleased to be traveling with you!
Counting on you!
A new friend, huh?
Great to have you!
Everyone,
please take good care of Navi.
We’ll all make sure to
look after her.
Ult, you look after Navi too, okay?
Yeah, yeah.
I’m heading out!
Have a nice trip!
Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie
Friede here!
It’s time to Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie!
Today’s topic is Trimmien!
Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie
Trimmien
Classification
Type
Height
Weight
Ability
Poodle Pokémon
Normal
Fur Coat
People cut its fur
and go wild over its various styles,
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
but do you know
which of these styles actually exists?
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
See the answer after the commercials!
Oh! One toss makes a red-white-spinny-shaky
Cutesy Capsule
One click makes a rolly-wobbly-all-aflutter
onlooking Street
One toss makes a red-white-spinny-shaky
Cutesy Capsule
One click makes a rolly-wobbly-all-aflutter
onlooking Street
Gonna give my motivation button a little tap!
The power of hard work is amazing!
(Ahem!)
But if I slack off I might end up devolving...
Well, that’s no good!
But now you mention it...
I know button mashing won’t help at all
So stop shaking this maiden’s heart already
(Stop it!)
Getting attached, but then they turn away
When things just don’t go the way that you want...
Isn’t it so fun? Doesn’t it make your heart race?
Doesn’t it make you all excited?
When I feel a spark...
I’ll catch it in a Cutesy Capsule
Face to face with the dream I’ve always imagined...
I’ve got electric jolts running through me!
I’m so lovey-dovey I can’t even move!
When I know change is still inside of me...
I’ll catch it in a Cutesy Capsule
then we can be together forever
We’ll conquer any obstacle!
I know our future will shine!
So let’s be friends!
Pick up you! I want you! Hit chu straight in the heart!
Pick up you! I want you! We’re right at the peak of our adven-chu!!
Oh! One toss makes a red-white-spinny-shaky
Cutesy Capsule
One click makes a rolly-wobbly-all-aflutter
onlooking Street
One toss makes a red-white-spinny-shaky
Cutesy Capsule
One click makes a rolly-wobbly-all-aflutter
onlooking Street
Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie
Time to announce
the correct answer!
The answer is...
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
Club Cut
Heart Cut
Spade Cut
B: Heart Cut!
Heart Cut
Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie
Cutting its fur doesn’t just give it
sharper fashion sense, but sharper reflexes, too!
You want to try this style?
Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie
S-So cute!
Next episode
Navi became one of
the Rising Voltteccers!
The Brave Asagi’s amazing!
It’s got everything!
Next episode
Ugh, a little kid gettin’ all riled up...
What’s with you, little kid Ult?
Huh?! I’m your senpai, y’know!
Navi, Ult... Can I ask you two
to run an errand?
Next episode
Huh?!
Why me?!
And so, to be continued
next time on Pocket Monsters!
Navi’s Little Big Adventure!
Navi's Little Big Adventure!